the humble shaker bottle
nobody and i mean nobody wants a chunky
mix of protein or pre-workout powder and
the right shaker bottle will be your
trusty companion that you really learn
to appreciate the second you do not have
it to mix your post workout slop
while shaker bottles are often
overshadowed by a set of weights they
might be one of the most essential
accessories that you can have to
maximize your gains and iceshaker is
really shaking up the game thanks to
their double vacuum sealed container
it's made from stainless steel and
instead of an annoying ball rolling
around in your bottle there's a screw-in
agitator that's meant to break up your
powder i've been testing out their line
of shakers for a few weeks so now it's
time for me to share my experience with
you in this review
what's up everybody it's jake back in my
happy place aka the barbing garage gym
and in full review today i have the ice
shaker bottle in this video we're going
to go over all the features the details
the price pros and cons and of course
who should and who should not buy this
shaker bottle
okay so before we get started today
as always i gotta let you guys know we
have reviewed a whole lot of shaker
bottles on barbin.com just do a quick
google search type in barbin best shaker
bottles our list is going to pop right
up for you and you can find out for
yourself which one takes home our top
spot
so let's start with the unboxing now of
the ice shaker as i said i received mine
a few weeks ago and there's a whole lot
of features i like about this bottle
that can't be ignored
let's start with the handle here
it's significantly larger than most
making it really easy for transportation
and you can hold more than just the
bottle in your hand it is made with that
stainless steel
but it also has a nice powder coat on it
giving it a matte black finish
might make it more durable but this
thing is going to be durable enough to
last you a very long time it does have a
vacuum sealed technology
making your cold drinks cold for about
30 hours and your hot drinks hot for
around 12 hours
and i got to say me personally i can't
stand that annoying rattling sound that
you often find with your standard shaker
bottle but thanks to the patented screw
and agitator here that's eliminated
completely making your experience
virtually silent
[Music]
okay so with all the good things being
said there are a few potential cons you
might run into with this shaker bottle
as always i tend to start with price so
we're gonna do the same thing here this
is listed around 30
you know that's expensive for a shaker
bottle you might not like that you may
want to opt for a cheaper plastic one
online
and since this is made with stainless
steel you'll notice your measurement
markings are on the inside it's really
just how it had to be done and that
might make it a little more difficult
when you're measuring your liquids
but it might not be that bad at the same
time
since this does have a tapered design
it's meant to fit in the majority of cup
holders but it's not guaranteed to fit
in your specific cup holder so make sure
that your cup holder can fit the three
inches that is the base of this bottle
before you put it in your car and try to
take it on the road
so as far as pricing goes
this is one of the more expensive
options available to you on the market
but since there are three different
sizing options there's also three
different pricing options so there's a
20 ounce version available for about 30
bucks this 26 ounce bottle it's around
35 and there is a 36 ounce bottle for
about 45
you can also make yours customizable for
an extra 10 bucks you can get color of
your choice personal engravings and even
various clip art to choose from now the
beauty of this bottle is you can also
turn it into a tumbler if you wanted to
there's a flex lid available for you to
purchase for an extra 10 bucks you can
get their straw and their brush to clean
the bottle it's another nine dollars and
you can even get a silicon boot to go on
the bottom
adding to your durability maybe even
making it more secure in your cup holder
for another eight bucks now when it's
all said and done
you're looking at maybe spending 80
bucks on a shaker bottle and that might
turn you away but this is also
compatible with cold and hot drinks and
thanks to the screw and agitator you can
even make alcoholic mixed drinks with it
if you want to so we're going to talk
about now how this bottle was
constructed starting with the lid it is
plastic but it's bpa free and you can
throw it in the dishwasher
as i mentioned this is made with
stainless steel and it does have that
powder coat this is one of the most
durable bottles you're gonna find and
does have that nice matte finish i was
talking about
since this bottle does not have a
pattern on it you can put this one in
the dishwasher and even dry it on low
heat but if you were to opt in for one
with a pattern it's best to hand wash it
so you don't wear away that pattern
[Music]
okay so i'm going to walk you through
some of the features now of the shaker
bottle and also you know just
demonstrate how to use it so starting
with the lid again it does have a nice
large handle making it super easy for
transportation say you're going to the
gym coming home you got your keys in
your hand super easy with this
does have a nice pop top easy to use it
will lock in place back here so it's not
going to you know smack you in the face
if you're drinking it whatever but make
sure you hear this click
before you start shaking it taking it on
the road it might leak out if you don't
do that i really like the rubber grip
also on the lid makes it once again
super easy makes it super easy to screw
on screw off you get a nice little grip
on it and my absolute favorite thing
about this shaker bottle it's the
screw-in agitator i cannot stand the
noise a metal ball makes rolling around
in my shaker all the time
with this i mean all you're gonna hear
is that liquid sloshing around
and you know once again the measurement
lines are on the inside of this bottle
it might be a little problematic in the
beginning when you're trying to find
that you know exact measurement but
after a couple tries i really found it
to be totally fine i had no issues at
all but you know while i got you here
let's mix some protein powder why not
nice i got water today
i'm a big milk guy with my protein
powder but for the sake of this video
we're going to use some water
all right mix that in
my nice scoop of protein
we're gonna get to shaking
as you can tell i mean the only noise
you're hearing right now
it's that liquid sloshing around all
right let's see how we did
unscrew the lid here
nice and smooth
there's really no chunks whatsoever left
behind
i mean
there's a few little specks you know on
the bottle but that's bound to happen
with any shaker bottle really but as you
can tell i mean
nice and smooth really
i don't taste any chunks i don't feel
any chunks whatsoever
okay so now we're gonna dig into who
should and should not buy this shaker
bottle if you're somebody who's on the
go a lot you're really gonna like the
large handle here makes it super easy to
you know have your keys in your hand
maybe hold a bag whatever it may be
makes it a lot easier and your cold
drinks are gonna stay cold for around 30
hours and your hot drinks are gonna stay
hot for about 12 hours not every shaker
bottle is gonna offer you that which i
think is really cool and because it's
made of stainless steel
super durable
it could be the last shaker bottle you
ever really need to buy
now on the flip side
people who should not buy it
this is kind of expensive at the end of
the day it's a shaker bottle this is 35
potentially more
meaning you know if that falls out of
your price range you can always opt in
for a plastic bottle anything cheaper
really there are cheaper ones available
and then the measurement lines
i really didn't find it too much of a
problem but if you do find it a problem
having the measurement lines on the
inside i would suggest maybe looking for
you know one of those plastic bottles
where you can see through it and you can
see all your measurement lines
accurately
thanks for watching everybody i hope
this video was really helpful and gave
you some more insight on what this
bottle has to offer
stay on the lookout for my next video
but as always head over to barbind.com
and read up more about this product just
search barbin ice shaker review
article is going to pull right up and
you can read over everything we
discussed here today i'll see y'all next
time
[Music]